tunalawsuit.com 2019-06-06

# Privacy Statement

Kurtzman Carson Consultants LLC (“KCC”) wants to make your on-line experience satisfying and safe. Our aim is to safeguard the privacy and security of your personal information while providing a personalized service that meets your individual preference and needs. At all times we comply with applicable laws and regulations governing the confidentiality and security of information we receive and maintain. This Privacy Statement describes KCC’s privacy practices for the services KCC provides through websites it creates, configures, and hosts on behalf of its clients and for the websites located at http://www.kccllc.com, http://www.kccllc.net, and http://classaction.kccllc.net. We process personal information pursuant to service agreements we have in place with our clients who have retained us to provide a variety of services on their behalf, including but not limited to class action administration, corporate restructurings, state insolvency proceedings, and litigation matters. The personal information that you or our clients provide to us is used to perform the various services that are described in each service agreement.

**What information do we obtain about you, how do we obtain it and what do we use it for?**

KCC collects personal information through our websites to enable us to provide our on-line services to our clients. When we say personal information, we mean information that is about you or that can help identify you. You may be asked to provide personal information such as your name, address, phone number, Social Security number, date of birth, employee identification number, geolocation data, e-mail address, and bank account details. We use Social Security numbers for many purposes, especially to comply with federal and state laws such as tax laws and anti-money-laundering laws. We also may receive personal information about you from a third party authorized by you, such as a class action defendant or another intermediary acting on your behalf.

Each site visitor (“User”) is provided with a dedicated website that houses all pertinent information regarding a specific legal case. KCC typically provides its services through websites that KCC creates, configures and hosts on behalf of the client. KCC operates its websites and collects usage data about Users at the direction of, and in accordance with, the instructions of KCC’s clients.

KCC’s arrangements with its clients may require KCC to provide all User information in KCC’s possession, including a User’s personal information, directly to the client with which the User is associated (i.e., the User’s employer). If a User corresponds with KCC, KCC may keep a record of that correspondence. KCC does not transfer any personal User information to any third party (other than KCC’s client) unless KCC is authorized to do so by the client with which the User is associated, in connection with the services that KCC provides to its client, or required to do so by applicable law.

We may share your information with KCC-affiliated companies and with other service providers as necessary. All such parties will be obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of the information and, except as may be required by law or governmental regulation, will be prohibited from further disclosing the information except in furtherance of the purposes for which it was disclosed, in which case such further disclosure will be subject to the same confidentiality and security obligations. We will not disclose your personal information to anyone outside these parties or sell to any parties for unsolicited marketing purposes.

Personal information you provide on this site is processed and stored in the United States and may be transferred to, processed and stored in countries outside the United States by KCC, its affiliates and service providers, all in accordance with this Privacy Statement. As KCC and its affiliated companies form part of a global group of companies, we may also disclose your personal information to overseas entities within the group who assist us in supplying our services including through data storage solutions, back-up services and IT support. These entities are generally located in Canada, New Zealand, the United Kingdom and Australia. We may also disclose your personal information to other overseas affiliates and service providers who assist us in supplying our services or who perform functions on our behalf, all in accordance with this Privacy Statement.

**Data Collection Technologies / Method Server Logs**  
In order to improve the quality of our website and services, we may from time to time send you what is known as a “cookie” as permitted by applicable laws and regulations. A cookie is a piece of text that a website transfers to your computer’s hard drive. This cookie does not allow KCC access to your hard drive, but it assists in identifying, for example, whether you have visited our website on a previous occasion. Only the site that posted the cookie can read it.

Please note that the websites to which this site may be linked may also make use of their own cookies to collect information from you. Most browsers will automatically accept a cookie, but it may be possible to set your browser to notify you prior to a cookie being sent at which point you can accept or reject it.

Additionally, we may collect information through the use of pixels, device IDs and similar technologies. A pixel is a line of code that is used by a website or third party to assign online activities to a computer or browser. The use of a pixel allows websites and us to record, for example, that a user has visited a particular website. Additional information from an earlier period or interaction may be included in the pixel. Currently, KCC does not respond to “Do Not Track” signals from browsers.

If you access an online service maintained by KCC or one of its affiliates we may use a tool called “Google Analytics” which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the opt-out service provided by Google.

We may share the information we collect via cookies and Google Analytics with our related entities including entities located outside of the United States who assist us in supplying our services including through data storage solutions, back-up services and IT support. These entities are generally located in Canada, New Zealand, the United Kingdom and Australia. We may also disclose it to others if required to do so by law.

**Third Party Collection of Personal Information**  
KCC does not permit third party collection of your personal information on this site. Links to third party websites may be provided on this site for informational or other purposes. KCC is not responsible for any personal information you may choose to submit to a third party website accessed from this site.

**Security Precautions to Protect Personal Information**  
We employ appropriate administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect your personal information and to ensure that it is not accessed by unauthorized persons. Information is encrypted for transfer wherever this is possible. Our security procedures may require you to provide proof of identification before we will release personal information to you. This proof may be in addition to any password required to gain access to our online service. Multiple incorrect attempts or invalidation will result in a lockout from the information. We undergo periodic reviews of our security policies and procedures to help ensure that our systems are secure and protected.  
KCC will never initiate an email to you requesting your personal information. If you have further questions about Identity Theft, you may find the US Federal Trade Commission website helpful.

Accessing and Updating Your Information  
KCC is committed to ensuring that the personal information it receives is accurate. At the direction of, and in accordance with, the instructions of KCC’s clients, KCC allows Users who make reasonable requests to access their personal information in KCC’s possession and to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate information. Users who have questions about personal information on file with KCC may, if the client so provides, access the client website to make such corrections or may contact KCC at the address below.

**Additional Information for EU/EEA Residents**  
In addition to the information provided above, if you are a current resident of an EU/EEA country, you may have certain rights regarding your personal information. KCC will assist our data controller clients, to the extent possible, with the fulfillment of their obligations to respond to your requests. These may include, depending on the circumstance, the right to access your personal information; rectify the personal information we hold about you; erase your personal information; restrict our use of your personal information; object to our use of your personal information; receive your personal information in a usable electronic format and transmit it to a third party (also known as the right of data portability); lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority; and withdraw any consent you have given to the uses of your personal information. If you would like to discuss or exercise the rights you may have, feel free to contact us via email or mail as described in the next section.

This Privacy Statement only applies to KCC websites and does not apply to any websites from which you may have linked to this website or to any website to which you may link from this website.

**Disclaimer**  
The services provided by a KCC website do not constitute the rendering of legal services, and no attorney-client relationship is formed between KCC and any client, or between KCC and any User, by virtue of such services. The information contained in KCC websites is not intended to constitute legal advice or to substitute for obtaining appropriate legal advice. This Privacy Statement describes KCC’s privacy practices only. It does not describe, and KCC makes no representations about, the privacy practices of any other parties, including KCC’s clients, who may receive personal information from KCC in the course of using KCC’s services.

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of KCC, or about KCC’s websites, please contact KCC at the following address:

Webmaster   
KCC  
222 N. Pacific Coast Highway, 3rd Floor  
El Segundo, California 90245  

**Changes to Privacy Statement**  
KCC may change this Privacy Statement from time to time. Each time you visit the website, please see the “Effective Date” to determine if it has been revised since the last time you entered the site. A “Revised” notation will serve as notice to you that a change has been made.

_Revised November 28, 2018_
